I ate seven pints of ice cream this week
and was still able to maintain a caloric
deficit. Here are the seven pints I ate
this week. I started off by recreating
Ben and Jerry's Peanut Butter World
flavor, which is chocolate ice cream
with peanut butter swirls and Oreo
swirls. It was insane. And then I did a
marshmallow sky flavor. This was also a
Ben & Jerry's recreation. Blue
marshmallow base with cookie dough and
little marshmallow pieces. Then I did
yet another Ben & Jerry's recreation.
And this was the Gimme S'mores flavor,
which was a toasted marshmallow base
with fudge flakes, Oreo, and topped with
graham cracker and marshmallow. Then I
did a coffee ice cream. I finally
perfected this recipe. It is so freaking
good. If you like coffee ice cream, you
are going to love this recipe. Speaking
of coffee ice cream, I turned that base
into one of my favorite flavors of all
time, coffee Oreo. I had all my friends
try this one and they loved it. Then I
decided to give Dairy Queen a little bit
of love. I recreated their S'mores
Blizzard. It's summertime. S'mores is
all the rage right now, so I had to give
it a shot. And I was not disappointed.
Then I ended off the week with yet
another Ben & Jerry's recreation. New
York Super Fuds Chunk. One of my
favorite flavors of all time.